teheadquarters.com 2019-05-20

# TeHeadQuarters.com - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how TeHeadquarters.com uses and protects any information that you give TeHeadquarters.com when you use this website.

TeHeadquarters.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

TeHeadquarters.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**Information Collected**  
In order to use this service a person must register using his or her contact information such as your name and email address. This information is used to login to use our service and to contact the member regarding our service and or products. Upon registration and each login your IP address is recorded. We use this information to provide our services and features to you, to improve those services, and to provide you with customer support.

**Personally Identifying Information**  
To take advantage of certain optional services of TE Headquarters, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifying information. Personally identifying information is information that could reasonably be used to identify you professionally (such as your full name, email address, and phone number), and which we may refer to here as “PII”. You are never obliged to provide this information and you can choose not to provide such information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in some services.  
No PII is collected automatically. Your personal information will not be shared with any other third party. The only personal information stored is the specific information provided on the signup form and your profile. No other information is stored, for example, via cross referencing with other databases or IP addresses. You may request that your personal information is deleted at any time, you may also request at any time to know what information we have stored from you. 

**Security**  
We take every precaution to protect our members information. Only the administrator of this website has access to members email address and other information. We do NOT sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

**Cookies and Log Files**  
Like many website operators, we sometimes make use of browser “cookies” to track user activity. A “cookie” is a small piece of  
information that we use to assign each visitor’s computer a unique, random numerical identification code that is stored on your computer. Cookies do not collect or store PII. Third party companies that advertise may use cookies and other tracking information.  
Cookies are optional on TE Headquarters. You can configure your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being set  
by choosing this option in the preferences or menu options in your browser. The server, that hosts this website, has log files that gather various technical information about the site usage. This information is anonymous. 

**Members right to Cancel**  
All members have a right to cancel their account at any time. A removal link can be found in the members menu.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**  
A member, at any time, may go to their account information and update their information.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments about our privacy policy you can contact us by sending an email to admin[at]teheadquarters.com
